unscramble_gold:
  question: "Gold"
  answer: "Gold"
  reward: 'random'
unscramble_mojang:
  question: "Mojang"
  answer: "Mojang"
  reward: 'random'
unscramble_minecraft:
  question: "Minecraft"
  answer: "Minecraft"
  reward: 'random'
unscramble_iron:
  question: "Iron"
  answer: "Iron"
  reward: 'random'
unscramble_Cactus:
  question: "Cactus"
  answer: "Cactus"
  reward: 'random'
unscramble_flower:
  question: "Flower"
  answer: "Flower"
  reward: 'random'
unscramble_lapis_lazuli:
  question: "Lapis Lazuli"
  answer: "Lapis Lazuli"
  reward: 'random'
unscramble_blaze:
  question: "Blaze"
  answer: "Blaze"
  reward: 'random'
unscramble_dragon:
  question: "Dragon"
  answer: "Dragon"
  reward: 'random'
unscramble_amethyst:
  question: "Amethyst"
  answer: "Amethyst"
  reward: 'random'
unscramble_diamond:
  question: "Diamond"
  answer: "Diamond"
  reward: 'random'
unscramble_enderman:
  question: "Enderman"
  answer: "Enderman"
  reward: 'random'
unscramble_blue:
  question: "Blue"
  answer: "Blue"
  reward: 'random'
unscramble_endermite:
  question: "Endermite"
  answer: "Endermite"
  reward: 'random'
unscramble_crying_cbsidian:
  question: "Crying Obsidian"
  answer: "Crying Obsidian"
  reward: "random"
unscramble_cbsidian:
  question: "Obsidian"
  answer: "Obsidian"
  reward: 'random'